Washington Star 061 061
Stage
- Series 23: Photograph Morgue
  - Sub-Series 1: Biographical
    - Woodell Pat (Actress) - Woods Tom (High Jump) (Collective Folders: WOODR) (Box 1522)
    - Woodson S Howard Jr (Howard) - WOR (Collective Folders: WOODW; WOOL; WOOT; WOR) (Box 1523)
    - Worden Alfred M (Astronaught NASA) - Wright Elmo (Sports) (Collective Folders: WR; WRA; WRE; WRIGHT; WRI) (Box 1524)
    - Wright, Frank Loyd (Architect) - Wriston Walter (Banker) (Collective Folders: WRIGHT JR; WRIGHT SZ) (Box 1525)
    - Wrong Hume - Wylie Ronald J (Collective Folders: WU; WY) (Box 1526)
    - Wyman Jane (Actress) - Yabes Maximo (US Medal of Honor) (Collective Folders: X; Y; YA) (Box 1527)
    - Yablonski Joseph - YAR (Collective Folders: YAM; YAN; YAR) (Box 1528)
    - Yarborough Cale (Auto Racing) - Yeatts Coleman B (VA Senator) (Collective Folders: YAT; YE) (Box 1529)
    - Yeh Chien Ying - Yonai Mitsumasa (Box 1530)
    - YORK - Youel Jim (Redksins Quarterback) (Collective Folders: YORK; YOS; YOU) (Box 1531)
    - Youlee Abee Fulbert (Pres Congo Republic) - Young David (Former White House Aide) (Collective Folders: YOUNG A; YOUNG B; YOUNG C; YOUNG D) (Box 1532)
    - Young E Merl - Young Loretta (Motion Picture Actress) (Collective Folders: YOUNG E; YOUNG F; YOUNG G; YOUNG H; YOUNG I; YOUNG J; YOUNG K; YOUNG L) (Box 1533)
    - Young Milton R (Senator) - Youngbloods The (Collective Folders: YOUNG M; YOUNG N; YOUNG O; YOUNG P; YOUNG Q; YOUNG R; YOUNG S; YOUNG T; YOUNG U; YOUNG V; YOUNG W) (Box 1534)
    - Youngdahl Luther (Judge) - Zachary Pat (Baseball) (Collective Folders: YU; Z; ZA; ZAB; ZAC) (Box 1535)
    - ZAG - Zapata Hialrio (Boxing) (Collective Folders: ZAG; ZAK; ZAH; ZAL; ZAM; ZAN) (Box 1536)
    - Zappa Frank - ZER (Collective Folders: ZAR; ZE; ZEC' ZEI; ZEL, ZEN; ZER) (Box 1537)
    - Zetterling Mai (Actress) - ZIM (Collective Folders: ZH; ZI; ZIE; ZIM) (Box 1538)
    - Zimbalist Efrem (Orchestra Conducter) - Zorn Jim (NFL Football) (Collective Folders: ZIN; ZIR; ZIS; ZIT; ZO) (Box 1539)
    - ZU - ZY (Collective Folders: ZU; ZY) (Box 1540)